[ Watch on KissFlix.co ]
[Live Forever]
[Episode 11]
What brings you here
today?
I've been wearing this gold bean
since I was born.
My mom told me
if it weren't for a savior
who blocked the car for her back then,
I wouldn't have had the chance
to come into this world.
This gold bean
was also given to me by that savior.
Later, we always wanted to see her again,
but we could never find her.
If you came to see me today
to tell a story from before you were born,
I might…
But how could she not be found?
Could it be
that she used a fake identity?
It's strange, too.
The impact of that car crash back then was huge,
yet she survived.
Song Yiqiu.
Why does the person in this photo
look exactly like you?
There are
plenty of people in this world who look alike.
You don't actually think
that I'm your savior, do you?
Right.
There really are a lot of people who look alike.
Lately, some fragmented images
that don't belong to this era
have inexplicably kept appearing
in my mind.
At first, I thought they were dreams
or hallucinations.
But it wasn't until I saw this photo
that I realized they weren't hallucinations.
And I'm not just Lin Huai of this lifetime.
We knew each other before.
You even
saved me in a past life.
Do you really not remember any of it?
There's a sniper. Go!
Don't stick your head out.
They didn't succeed.
They'll come for you again.
Run!
No, I'm not leaving.
You're awake?
That student.
Is he still alive?
Don't worry.
He's not dead.
That's good.
I'll go check on him.
Who is he?
Is he worth it for you, Song Yiqiu,
actually, Song Baiwei,
to have your heart pierced through
and your lungs shredded by bullets,
yet still worry about his life and death?
I can't explain it to you.
If I hadn't arrived fast enough,
you and that student would be dead already.
And
all the reporters in Shanghai
are waiting outside Ning Mansion
to see how your wound healed
and how you rose from the dead.
You put yourself
under everyone's flashbulbs.
You'll be dissected like a monster.
In these three thousand years,
haven't you suffered enough for this?
The land was torn apart.
Dynasties changed.
Haven't you seen enough?
Can you really save so many people?
I can't save them all.
But I'll save as many as I can.
It's because I've seen too much death
that I know how precious it is to live.
You used to be like this too.
You've changed.
That Ning Changyue
can't protect you.
Starting today,
you will stay here.
You are not allowed to go anywhere.
You want to lock me up?
It's for your protection.
Extra! Extra!
Commander Ning kills five innocent patrol officers
in a fit of rage to protect his wife.
Extra! Extra!
Commander Ning kills…
I want to see Commander Ning!
Sorry, you can't go in.
Calm down. You can't go in!
Let me in!
Commander,
Patrol Officer Chen Gensheng's family won't leave.
Let her in.
I'll handle the family.
You don't need to…
Let her in.
Yes, Sir.
Commander Ning!
You can't go in. You really can't.
Let her in.
Here.
Commander Ning.
What the newspaper says isn't true, is it?
That day, my son
was just following the order to disperse the students.
He…
He didn't even carry a gun.
He didn't do anything wrong.
He didn't kill anyone.
Commander Ning, I beg you.
I beg for your mercy.
-Please release him. -Give her the pension.
Pension?
No!
My son is not dead!
He's still in prison!
Give her double.
I don't want money!
I want my son!
Give me back my son!
You killed my son!
You butcher!
I want you to die a horrible death!
I'll take you down with me!
Granny!
Take her to the hospital! Hurry!
Somebody!
Hurry!
Granny.
Let's go.
Take it slow.
Be careful.
To the hospital. Hurry!
How many times has this been?
[Commander Ning kills five innocent patrol officer]
[in a fit of rage to protect his wife]
What is this now?
Explain.
Explain that you didn't know.
Explain that you did so to protect me.
Explain that they were in the wrong,
and you just did the right thing.
Explain it!
I'm investigating who tried to kill you.
They obviously came prepared.
It's very dangerous.
So I must…
Very dangerous.
So you'd rather kill these five innocent people.
Ning Changyue.
Now you've climbed step by step
to the position you wanted.
These five lives mean nothing to you,
just ants, is that it?
Commander Ning.
Treating human lives like weeds.
Abusing your power.
Is this your so-called protection?
Where are you going?
I'm leaving here.
It's very dangerous outside right now.
At any moment, you could…
Die,
or be treated as an immortal monster?
Ning Changyue.
I'm not afraid of these.
What I'm afraid of is that you let more people
die under your power in the name of protecting me.
Ning Changyue.
If I had known I would end up like this,
I would rather have died in Southern Qin back then.
[Tomb of Mr. Chen Gensheng]
[Tomb of Ms. Song Baiwei]
Turn it over.
Song…
Baiwei?
It really is you.
You were shot in the heart.
You couldn't have survived.
Are you
a human
or a ghost?
Did you erect this?
Song Baiwei.
I didn't expect that in your few short decades of life,
someone would sincerely
erect a tombstone for you.
That's nice.
Apples are okay.
I don't like pears.
You came to visit a grave with just a newspaper?
Are you trying to fool a ghost?
No, no, no.
That day, I thought you were dead.
In your briefcase,
I saw your name, Song Baiwei,
and the sketches.
Then,
I sent them to the newspaper.
Take a look.
It's him.
Thank you, Lin.
I didn't expect these drawings
to end up being sent to the newspaper.
It's nothing.
My pleasure.
I'll repay your kindness
in my next life.
Since you think I'm already dead,
then I'll just be a ghost.
[One month later]
Excuse me. Excuse me.
Miss, do you need a ride?
It's cheap and fast.
To the newspaper office.
Okay. Let's go.
Thank you.
Miss.
Do ghosts have to pay for a ride too?
Song Yiqiu.
I've already guessed your secret.
But in my heart,
you will always be Song Baiwei.